tralix.com 2002-12-07

# - Tralix, way beyond email

Tralix takes your privacy seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy. 

**What This Privacy Policy Covers**

This policy covers how Tralix treats personal information that Tralix collects and receives, including information related to your past use of Tralix products and services. Personal information is information about you that is personally identifiable like your name, address, email address, or phone number, and that is not otherwise publicly available.

This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that Tralix does not own or control or to people that Tralix does not employ or manage.

Tralix is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of any other web sites to which we link.

**Information Tracked**

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our web site. We also track browser types to help us understand our visitors' needs related to our web site design. 

Our site's optional information request forms require your name, company, e-mail address, as well as information to help us determine your needs related to our solution. We use this information to send updates and newsletters about our company and our products and also contact you if requested or necessary. You may opt-out of receiving future emails; if you wish to do this, simply follow the instructions at the end of any email sent through the Tralix system.

**Information Sharing and Disclosure**

Tralix does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you or Tralix customers with other people or non-affiliated companies except to provide products or services you've requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances:

  * We respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims.
  * We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of Tralix's terms of use, or as otherwise required by law.
  * We transfer information about you if Tralix is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, Tralix will notify you before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

**Security and Privacy**

Tralix web site uses security measures to protect against the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. We store the information in a database in a very secure environment at our Internet Datacenter provider (Exodus a C&W Company, Austin, TX).

**Cookies**

Tralix doesn’t use or create cookies on your computer. We believe cookies are an invasion in your privacy, so we don’t use cookies in our web site or in our permission marketing service.

Tralix takes care to reinforce the importance of our web site visitors' security and privacy among our employees. The bottom-line is that because our business involves hosting application accounts, data security is paramount. We're constantly re-evaluating and deploying new technologies to enhance our security.

**Notification of Privacy Policy Changes**

Tralix may update this policy. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your Tralix account or by placing a prominent notice on our site. 

**Encryption**

In certain areas or products, Tralix uses industry-standard SSL encryption or blowfish encryption with a 192 bit key to protect data transmissions.

**Questions and Suggestions**

If you have questions or suggestions, please contact us at:

**Tralix**  
2204 Lockwood Cove  
Austin Texas  
78723-3216, United States

**By Web**
